ruzeshoes.com 2014-12-19

# Privacy Policy | Ruzeshoes.com | Online Discount Shoes

Object reference not set to an instance of an object.

**Privacy & Security Policy**

Thank you for shopping with Ruze Shoes. We are committed to protecting your privacy and have established a Privacy & Security statement to keep you informed.

**1\. Information Collection**

When you make a purchase from Ruze Shoes (Site), we collect your personal information to fulfill your purchase, as well as register you an account for future purchases, wish lists, and record keeping. Ruze Shoes will not sell your personal information to third party companies for their promotional purposes.

Cookies: Like many sites, Ruze Shoes applies cookies to recognize you, track your usage on the site, and speed-up your navigation of the site. Most browsers are setup to already accept cookies. If you have your browser set to not accept cookies, you will not be able to access certain parts of the Site.

Age: Ruze Shoes will neither knowingly, nor intentionally, collect personal information from children under the age of 13. We require that you are either 18 years of age or using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us. 

**2\. Information Use and Disclosure**

Internal Use: Ruze Shoes uses your personal information to fulfill and process your order. We may internally use your personal information for our own marketing efforts and to determine a general marketplace about visitors to the Site.

Communications: Ruze Shoes will use your personal information to communicate with you about the Site. This includes, but not limited to, communications about your order, deliveries and confirmation emails with registering with us.

**3\. Data Security**

For financial transactions, Ruze Shoes takes proper procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, as well as on our physical facility. Only employees who perform a specific, related job are granted access to your personal information. While Ruze Shoes takes strong precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot 100% guarantee complete security.

**4\. Updates**

If Ruze Shoes changes or updates the Privacy & Security Policy, we will post them on the Site so that you are aware of it. If you have any questions about our Privacy & Security Policy, please contact us at (888) 544-1711 or at info@ruzeshoes.com.

_Last updated March 7, 2012_

Sincerely,

Ruze Shoes Security Team
